a lot easier on the west coast.
>> Well, thank you guys for for hanging. Um
so, um I will start with a little
opening statement then and ask you ask
away. Um but, uh Antonio Williams,
Clemson wide receiver. Um really, uh
really really impressed by Antonio. We
had him in on a 30 visit and uh really
liked him. Uh, you know, Lance Newark
and I went out there during uh the
season and got a chance to talk to Davo
and and Woody McCorvy out there. They
spoke extremely highly of him. Um,
Dustin Reagan, our area scout, really
swears by him. Had a great talk with him
before we made the pick. And um, so
really a top-notch young man. Uh, super
hard worker, consistent, the same guy
every day. um high high FBI, can
multi-line, understands the game,
understands zone, understands a man,
understands how to win. Um and he's
super competitive and he's super tough.
Um played through broken ribs last year
in 2024. Really fought through a
hamstring injury this year, which which
really limited his um you know, his
production, but played through the whole
thing. So, this guy's a tough kid. when
you go back and watch his his 2024 film,
you really get to see what what a
special talent he is. Um, so, uh, I'd
describe him just a just a great
athlete. Great athlete, really fast. Um,
and he's fast in a lot of different
ways. He's fast at the 40 time. The GPS
is really, really high on him in game
and then the old scouts eye. You see
him, he plays fast and he plays at a
high level. Uh, he's an NFL route
runner. He can win versus press. He can
he can beat man coverage. Um and so we
really like the versatility of him as
well. He uh he can play inside. He
played a lot of inside this year. He
played outside last year. And that's
really the the thing that differentiated
him from a lot of guys is winning
outside and winning against really good
players outside, especially in 2024. So,
uh NFL route runner. Um there's just a
lot of really really good things about
him and uh just all around great
package. So thrilled to have him,
thrilled to have him at the wide
receiver room and um just uh happy good
couple days here. So go ahead.
>> With the inside outside, how would you
project him or see him here and what
skills allow him to be productive maybe
inside and out?
>> Yeah, that's a great question. Well, I
think um yeah, if he he can play Z and F
and or or you know Z in in slot and so
um he'll he'll work at both of those. Uh
the things that he can show you he can
play outside. He's he's not he's not
huge, but he's not small. He's just a
hair under six feet and he's he's a
really tough player and he's got really
good releases and he plays really fast.
So those things allow him to win on the
outside uh versus versus bigger corners.
So even though he's not a 6'4 guy, he
can still win on the outside and and his
speed and his releases and his route
running and his details allow allow him
to do that. And the same thing with
inside is is he can he can win with his
quickness as well.
>> Was there a thing that jumped out to you
when you were watching him?
>> Uh I I think there there's a lot of
games. I think the the one that really
sold it for me was uh playing Georgia
last in 2024 and just seeing him play
outside and just seeing how win like uh
you see NFL guys win on Sundays.
>> You mentioned his route running. What
stood out to you on tape about that?
>> Just the the speed and the detail and
the precision and the quickness in and
out of breaks. You know, he he doesn't
look like a college guy out there and
and that's how they describe him, too.
He's, you know, he's he's meticulous
with his details and and just really
like when we went and saw him like he's
he's practicing and it wasn't whether
it's a walkth through or or a full speed
practice, he's taken it serious and you
saw that all come together on the field.
>> I know you guys try to stick to the
board generally, but how important was
it to to add to that room to get another
receiver in this draft?
>> Yeah, it was it was really important to
get a receiver uh somewhere in this
draft. you know, we thought I mean, we
have, you know, we could have gone
anywhere and I I think um we actually we
stuck to our board and he was the
highest guy on our board when we picked
and um you know, it happened to be at a
position that, you know, we could really
use it. So, uh it's nice when that comes
together and um yeah, we're thrilled to
have another guy in the receiver room.
>> The um you're saying he can play
obviously outside, but he was inside
last year. Does that change anything for
you in terms of how you looked at Luke
or Jaylen, two guys you've drafted
recently as well?
>> No. No, I it's just great competition.
It really is. And those guys will all
will all battle and um I think I really
like the competition and they're all
highly competitive guys and they're good
teammates. So, I think it'll add to a
really good culture in that room and
with with Coach Ingram.
>> Obviously, free agency whenever this
draft is over, we'll probably open up
again. Are you you've added enough
players? Do you feel like you kind of
have your room or do you still think
you're going to add more?
>> We're always adding all the way all the
way till the last game.
Hey, Adam. You said that the scouts
really was high on him and they vouched
a lot for him. What was some of those
extra tangibles that really stood out
for them that sold them on him?
>> Yeah, that's that's a great question.
And and like like I said earlier, Dustin
Reagan did a great job. He's he's an
outstanding area scout and um just that
they really really speak extremely
highly of him and he's been like that
his whole career. very consistent every
day. Very detailed, very hardworking,
just really uh a pros pro in his
approach in in every facet. And there's
a lot of guys we really like and trust
there. And uh they shoot us straight and
you know, they couldn't speak highly
enough about them. They go out of their
way to sit and say great things about
them.
>> When you talk about toughness, uh how
much do you value that at a position
like receiver where so much is involves
with skill and speed and things? Does
toughness really matter more in your
mind or as much? I mean, where is that
as a value kind of thing when you
evaluate a guy?
>> It's very important and it's very
important for a lot of different
reasons. Um, you know, just mental and
physical toughness and that's every
single position in football. You you got
to be tough both mentally and physically
and and he showed both of both of those
things just pushing through injuries and
and then also on the field the way he
blocks. I I I don't think I mentioned
that earlier. He's a good blocker as
well. He's a willing blocker. He's a
tough blocker. Uh, and he's willing to
to sell out over the middle. You know,
there's there's a lot of plays where
he's he's he's pretty uh you know, he's
exposed, but he'll go up and get it and
he's not worried about getting hit and
that that that impressed me a lot, too.
Actually, I I saw that and, you know, I
wasn't expecting that and then seeing
that on the tape, it was really a
pleasant surprise.
>> Hey, Adam, you kind of just um answered
one of the questions I had because I sat
a quick clip. I think you saw him doing
a good bit of blocking, but he just
shared with Antonio just shared with us
um on the call that he refers to himself
kind of as like a smooth operator. So,
so I you know does that resonate with
you and what your kind of reaction has
been when you watch the the film and
when you have seen him in person?
>> Yeah, his nickname is going to be
Shotti, I think. Oh, but he uh we'll
call him that forever now. Um but no, he
is he is he's really he makes it look
easy and and his speed is easy and so um
you know I can I can see that. But yeah,
the you really see like a really
technique sound like smooth player out
on the field. Yeah.
>> Adam, when you look at kind of your
draft history of wide receiver here, is
it fair to say that height size isn't
necessarily a dominating trait that that
you guys are concerned with? And I guess
why would that be?
>> No, I think it's just kind of how the
how the board falls and how we're
looking at guys. And um you know, I
think in this particular case, and
everybody every case is different, but
um you know, he's not he's not huge, but
he's not small either. And and neither
is neither is Luke. Luke's Luke's pretty
big, too. Um and so, you know, where
where they're not the the 6'2, 63, 6'4
guys. Um, but they they can play, you
know, and they can run and they can do
the other things that that maybe allow
you to play outside.
>> Hey, good evening, Adam. Is it really
unique? Like a lot of receivers can
create space off the line of scrimmage,
create space in their break, but a guy
that can create space in their STEM as
well. Is that is that really kind of
unique? Yeah, I think he's really
advanced for for a college player and
those are those are the things you you
usually learn in the NFL level and just
th those nuances as as you grow as a
player, as you learn new things and
everything like that. And he looks like
that already. And I think that that was,
you know, what I was trying to express
is that all those different things like
those are the things that'll win at our
level and he's already doing them. And
so it makes it an easier evaluation when
you see that on the tape and you don't
have to project it. A lot of times you
have to project those things. You can
see it in their movements. You can see
it in sometimes how they move with the
ball in their hands rather than as a
route runner because a lot of times
they're not asked to run certain routes
or the route tree isn't as as diverse in
in college football as is in the pros.
So you have to project a lot. But with
him you see it and you see it uh
consistently and you see him win with
it. And then his his drop rate was near
10% in 2024, less than 2% in 2025. Uh so
obviously a big improvement there. Uh
can you recollect anything from the from
the studies that kind of point to that
improvement or was any of it tied to his
moving more outside to more inside in
2025?
>> Yeah, I think you know sometimes there's
a little bit of variance in in that. But
in terms of just watching him and
watching his catching skills live, you
know that that helps a lot when you
watch them in person and then watch them
you know throughout his career and
everything. I always I I actually
thought he had really good hands.
>> Yeah.
>> Adam, when you look at Antonio's game,
how do you feel like it it might
complement the way Terry McLaren plays?
>> Yeah, I think um you know, I think
Terry,
you you see Terry can do just about
everything, right? And and certainly
take the top off the defense and and
yeah, he's a great deep ball receiver.
Antonio will be able to do he you could
see him play vertically also but he's
really good underneath and so you can
see him really helping us out on third
down. So we'll have multiple guys that
you know you'll have multiple guys
across the formation that can win on
third down and I think um you know not
only him and Terry but the rest of the
guys and and so it just adds one more to
that group. So he's he's quick and he's
fast and he's a you know just a really
good route runner. So, um I think if you
compare those probably he's he's more of
the underneath guy than Terry, but
certainly um versatile enough to do all
the rest of the stuff.
>> Last one,
>> Adam. Um with tomorrow, obviously coming
up and a couple more picks than you guys
have had. Are you hoping to accomplish
anything specific or is it just more
general run-of-the-mill best player on
the board kind of thing?
>> Yeah, there there's really nothing where
we got to say, okay, we have to go get
this position or anything like that. So,
we're going to get the best guys on the
board, the best commanders, and guys
that fit us and can help, you know, add
to this this culture, this team, the
competition, the depth, and and just
raise the level of this team. So, we
have uh we have some good picks and and
looking forward to getting them.
>> Thanks,
>> All right. Thanks, guys.
>> All right.
numbers.
>> I saw